question_data = [
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False",
                       "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True",
                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;",
                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
                       "correct_answer": "True",
                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                      {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                       "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]


# to check the working of dict inside the list
# print(question_data[-1]['question'])
#
# for q in question_data:
#     print(q['category'])

